<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Carrier | Someth Victory]]></title>
  <link href="http://somethvictory.github.io/blog/categories/carrier/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://somethvictory.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-05T22:00:24+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://somethvictory.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Someth Victory]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving Yoolk Inc.]]></title>
    <link href="http://somethvictory.github.io/blog/2015/08/10/leaving-yoolk-inc/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-10T19:32:33+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://somethvictory.github.io/blog/2015/08/10/leaving-yoolk-inc</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It has been more than 5 years and a half that I had been working at Yoolk, and
today is my last day here. Time seemed to fly so fast, that I couldn&rsquo;t remember everything. What I never forget from Yoolk is
the best time we had with best people there. Developers at Yoolk are very
skillful and talented. They are very helpful and friendly. Yoolk itself is one
of the best Tech Companies in Cambodia I could say. It&rsquo;s using as well as
contributing to latest open source technologies from the community. Yoolk got a
very good design principle in software development following by best practises
with OOdesign, Design Pattern, TDD/BDD, etc&hellip;</p>

<p>Yoolk had provided me very good opportunities to grow my professional skill from
very ground floor position. I did learn a lot while working there. People at Yoolk not
only provided me chances to improve my skills, but gave me very good time to
enjoy as well. They are not only colleagues, but good friends as well. Really thanks you guys!</p>

<p>Leaving Yoolk is the hardest decision I have ever made. It is the most
frustrated time I would say, maybe because Yoolk is my first comapny
I worked for and I&rsquo;d been there for quite a long time. But nothing remains the
same. Life is about moving forward I left Yoolk in order to find a futher improvement, opportunity, and explore a new world.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
